Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
In this world, there are hundreds of kinds of scent.
في هذا العالم، هناك المئات من أنواع الروائح.
My name is Win Wongsawat,
اسمي وين وونغساوات
and I can "smell" spiritual energy.
وأستطيع أن "أشم" الطاقة الروحية.
Well, actually, I can smell all the scents in this world.
حسنًا، في الواقع، أستطيع أن أشعر بجميع الروائح في هذا العالم.
I was born with a hypersensitive sense of smell,
لقد ولدت مع حاسة شم شديدة الحساسية،
whether they are physical scents
سواء كانت روائح مادية
like food,
مثل الطعام،
desserts,
الحلويات،
detergents,
المنظفات،
perfumes,
العطور،
and flowers,
والزهور
or intangible ones
أو غير الملموسة
like virtue,
مثل الفضيلة،
evil,
شر،
love,
حب،
greed,
جشع،
wrath,
الغضب
and obsession,
والهوس
each with its own distinct scent.
كل منها له رائحة مميزة.
And lastly, there's spiritual energy.
وأخيرًا، هناك الطاقة الروحية.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Hey, Win!
مهلا، وين!
Wait there at the restaurant.
انتظر هناك في المطعم.
Something happened to your fortune-telling client.
لقد حدث شيء ما لعميلك الذي يقرأ لك الطالع.
I'm picking them up right now.
أنا ألتقطهم الآن.
Sure. Hurry, then.
بالتأكيد. اسرع إذن.
I'm sleepy and it's cold.
أنا نعسان والجو بارد.
The A/C here is freezing me to death.
مكيف الهواء هنا يجمدني حتى الموت.
Okay, okay.
حسنًا، حسنًا.
- One iced Americano, please. - Yes, just a moment.
- كوب واحد من الأمريكانو المثلج من فضلك. - نعم، لحظة واحدة فقط.
Whose jacket is this?
لمن هذه السترة؟
The scent of summer?
رائحة الصيف؟
Who...
من...
(My Secret Of Seer The Series)
(سلسلة سر الرائي)
Sometimes I can't tell if this is reality, a dream…
أحيانًا لا أستطيع أن أقول إن هذا هو الواقع أم مجرد حلم...
or some other world.
أو أي عالم آخر.
Who's there?!
من هناك؟!
Please...
لو سمحت...
Are you ready?
هل انت مستعد؟
Are you ready?!
هل أنت مستعد؟!
This dream again.
هذا الحلم مرة أخرى.
(Tarot Cards For Making Millions)
(بطاقات التارو لكسب الملايين)
Venerable Father,
أيها الأب الجليل،
this batch looks smaller than usual.
تبدو هذه الدفعة أصغر من المعتاد.
Win.
يفوز.
Your bad luck year can be fatal.
قد يكون عام الحظ السيئ الخاص بك قاتلاً.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
you'll encounter many inexplicable events.
سوف تواجه العديد من الأحداث التي لا يمكن تفسيرها.
Here.
هنا.
Thank you, Venerable Father.
شكرا لك يا أبانا الجليل.
But...
لكن...
I already know these kinds of things.
أنا أعرف بالفعل هذا النوع من الأشياء.
It won't suffice.
لن يكون كافيا.
But why do they want to take my life?
ولكن لماذا يريدون أن يأخذوا حياتي؟
That I do not know.
أنني لا أعلم.
But a highly virtuous individual is your refuge.
لكن الفرد الفاضل للغاية هو ملجأك.
A highly virtuous individual?
فرد فاضل للغاية؟
Who is it?
من هذا؟
You have a better sense of smell than I do.
لديك حاسة شم أفضل مني.
Use it.
استخدمه.
Use it to your advantage.
استخدمه لصالحك.
That person will save you from demise.
هذا الشخص سوف ينقذك من الهلاك.
They should not be far from your reach.
لا ينبغي أن تكون بعيدة عن متناولك.
But the most important thing is,
ولكن الشيء الأكثر أهمية هو،
you must not travel out of the city at all.
لا يجوز لك السفر خارج المدينة على الإطلاق.
Sadhu.
سادهو.
I hope today brings only good things!
أتمنى أن يحمل اليوم أشياء جيدة فقط!
Win, dude!
الفوز يا صديقي!
- Win! - You've got the keycard!
- فوز! - لقد حصلت على البطاقة الرئيسية!
Use it!
استخدمها!
Win! What the hell have you been doing?
فوز! ماذا كنت تفعل بحق الجحيم؟
Your client, the heir of a gold shop, is waiting for you!
عميلك وريث محل الذهب في انتظارك!
The session starts at 9:30 A.M., no?
تبدأ الجلسة الساعة 9:30 صباحًا، أليس كذلك؟
Look at the time.
أنظر إلى الوقت.
It's already 9:45!
إنها الساعة 9:45 بالفعل!
Shit!
اللعنة!
- Go. Now! - I'm screwed!
- اذهب الآن! - أنا في ورطة!
So how is it, Master?
فكيف الحال يا سيدي؟
Why is it taking you so long?
لماذا يستغرق الأمر منك وقتا طويلا؟
Well, it's...
حسنا، إنه...
Well what? Just say it!
حسناً ماذا؟ فقط قلها!
I'm cool with whatever result.
أنا راضٍ عن النتيجة مهما كانت.
Well...
حسنًا...
Is it possible for you to withdraw your shares right away?
هل من الممكن أن تقوم بسحب أسهمك مباشرة؟
This isn't your time.
هذا ليس وقتك
Huh?
هاه؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Is it gonna be a loss?
هل ستكون خسارة؟
Or a profit?
أو الربح؟
That's all I want to know. Will I make a loss or a profit?
هذا كل ما أريد معرفته. هل سأخسر أم أربح؟
I don't have many options, do I?
ليس لدي الكثير من الخيارات، أليس كذلك؟
That's all I want to find out.
هذا كل ما أريد معرفته.
Come on.
تعال.
Stop wasting time.
توقف عن إضاعة الوقت.
Do you even know how to read fortunes?
هل تعرف حتى كيفية قراءة الطالع؟
I've got other things to do, you know?
لدي أشياء أخرى للقيام بها، هل تعلم؟
Please give me a moment.
من فضلك أعطني لحظة.
This scent... He's certainly running on borrowed money.
هذه الرائحة... إنه بالتأكيد يستخدم أموالاً مقترضة.
I think...
أظن...
Think what?
فكر ماذا؟
It'll be catastrophic.
سيكون الأمر كارثيا.
You're definitely doomed.
لقد حُكم عليك بالهلاك بالتأكيد.
Hey!
يا!
How is that possible?
كيف ذلك ممكنا؟
I've poured so much into it!
لقد بذلت الكثير فيه!
I shouldn't have asked you for a reading.
لا ينبغي لي أن أطلب منك القراءة.
- This is unacceptable! - Please wait a moment, Mr. King.
- هذا غير مقبول! - من فضلك انتظر لحظة، سيد الملك.
Would you like to read other aspects instead?
هل ترغب في قراءة جوانب أخرى بدلا من ذلك؟
Anything else you're still worried about?
هل هناك أي شيء آخر لا يزال يقلقك؟
I only came for one thing.
لقد جئت لشيء واحد فقط.
That's it. I've had enough.
هذا كل شيء. لقد اكتفيت.
- Mr. King! - Disappointing!
- السيد الملك! - مخيب للآمال!
- I'm not paying. - Please wait!
- لن أدفع. - من فضلك انتظر!
- Mr. King! - Hey, Namo.
- السيد الملك! - مرحبا، نامو.
Let him go.
دعوه يذهب.
Come on, man.
هيا يا رجل.
A client's satisfaction can go both ways.
رضا العميل يمكن أن يذهب في كلا الاتجاهين.
You're a bastard yourself.
أنت لقيط بنفسك.
Only bringing me shady clients.
أحضر لي فقط العملاء المشبوهين.
What? How am I supposed to know?
ماذا؟ كيف لي أن أعرف؟
I don't have smelling senses like you!
ليس لدي حاسة شم مثلك!
What do we do next?
ماذا نفعل بعد ذلك؟
We don't have that many clients this month.
ليس لدينا الكثير من العملاء هذا الشهر.
There are barely any, even.
هناك بالكاد أي منها.
I've already dealt with old clients.
لقد تعاملت بالفعل مع العملاء القدامى.
I paid for ads and promoted the page, but it got reported...
لقد دفعت مقابل الإعلانات وقمت بالترويج للصفحة، ولكن تم الإبلاغ عنها...
What should we do?
ماذا يجب علينا أن نفعل؟
That's right. I'm Win Wongsawat.
هذا صحيح. أنا وين وونغساوات.
I can smell spiritual energy.
أستطيع أن أشعر بالطاقة الروحية.
Most of the time, it's just the scents.
في أغلب الأحيان، الأمر يتعلق فقط بالروائح.
But if it's strong, I can hear them too.
ولكن إذا كانت قوية، أستطيع أن أسمعهم أيضًا.
When my mind is weak, they show themselves in 8K Ultra HD.
عندما يكون عقلي ضعيفًا، تظهر هذه الأعراض بتقنية 8K Ultra HD.
I can smell everything in this world.
أستطيع أن أشم كل شيء في هذا العالم.
By everything, I really mean it.
بكل ما أقوله، أعني ذلك حقًا.
Including spiritual energy,
بما في ذلك الطاقة الروحية،
which is unique to each spirit.
والتي هي فريدة من نوعها لكل روح.
However, all of these require interpretation.
ومع ذلك، فإن كل هذه الأمور تتطلب التفسير.
I myself haven't explored every scent, either.
أنا أيضًا لم أستكشف كل الروائح بنفسي.
Shit!
اللعنة!
This always happened at every workplace I was in.
لقد حدث هذا دائمًا في كل مكان عمل كنت فيه.
And I'd get scolded by my boss,
وسوف أتعرض للتوبيخ من قبل رئيسي،
have my salary cut,
تم تخفيض راتبي
and become a gossip topic among colleagues.
وتصبح موضوعًا للحديث بين الزملاء.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I'm staying at Namo's father's condo,
أنا أقيم في شقة والد نامو،
as I couldn't afford a roof over my head.
لأنني لم أتمكن من تحمل تكاليف الحصول على سقف فوق رأسي.
Luckily, he's generous enough to let me stay
لحسن الحظ، فهو كريم بما يكفي للسماح لي بالبقاء
until I can afford my own place.
حتى أتمكن من تحمل تكاليف مكاني الخاص.
I spent days and nights looking for work,
لقد قضيت أيامًا وليالي في البحث عن عمل،
until I realized that I could make a living with fortune-telling.
حتى أدركت أنني أستطيع أن أعيش من خلال قراءة الطالع.
However, with this card...
ومع ذلك، مع هذه البطاقة...
Guardian spirits and your karmic creditors are coming for you
أرواح الحارس ودائنيك الكرميين قادمون إليك
to remind you to pray and make merit.
لتذكيرك بالصلاة والعمل الصالح.
They're waiting for your offerings.
إنهم ينتظرون عروضكم.
So this card means you have to make merits ASAP!
لذا فإن هذه البطاقة تعني أنه يتعين عليك تحقيق المزايا في أقرب وقت ممكن!
This is a warning.
هذا تحذير.
However, if you don't have the time to do so, feel free to reach out to me.
ومع ذلك، إذا لم يكن لديك الوقت للقيام بذلك، فلا تتردد في التواصل معي.
I have sacred blessings to help.
لدي بركات مقدسة لمساعدتي.
Whoa...
واو...
It's clear.
انها واضحة.
Your partner is cheating on you.
شريكك يخونك.
Are you serious?
هل انت جاد؟
Just as I thought...
كما اعتقدت...
What should I do, Namo?
ماذا يجب أن أفعل، نامو؟
I don't know either.
انا أيضا لا اعرف.
I also got dumped.
لقد تم التخلي عني أيضًا.
This was when I realized strange scents clouded them.
في تلك اللحظة أدركت أن هناك روائح غريبة تملأ المكان.
I've been doing fortune-telling since I was a sophomore.
لقد كنت أقوم بقراءة الطالع منذ أن كنت في السنة الثانية من الجامعة.
That was when I learned about tarot cards.
في ذلك الوقت تعلمت عن بطاقات التارو.
I taught myself everything.
لقد علمت نفسي كل شيء.
Win,
يفوز،
your reading is spot on.
قراءتك في محلها.
But honestly, I already knew that somewhat.
ولكن بصراحة، كنت أعرف ذلك بالفعل إلى حد ما.
I'll put an end to this.
سأضع حدا لهذا.
Excellent. You're doing the right thing.
ممتاز. أنت تفعل الشيء الصحيح.
This is heartbreaking.
هذا أمر محزن للغاية.
Back then, I studied fortune-telling only to help out my friends.
في ذلك الوقت، كنت أدرس علم التنجيم فقط لمساعدة أصدقائي.
However, nobody knew that I'd be making a living with this art.
ولكن لم يكن أحد يعلم أنني سأعيش من هذا الفن.
Right.
يمين.
Tong, the lighting's set.
تونغ، مجموعة الإضاءة.
How is it? His face doesn't look sickly, does it?
كيف حاله؟ وجهه لا يبدو مريضًا، أليس كذلك؟
Look at the camera, Win.
أنظر إلى الكاميرا، وين.
Yeah. Good to go.
نعم، جاهز للذهاب.
- Alright. - All set?
-حسنا. - هل كل شيء جاهز؟
Are you ready?
هل انت مستعد؟
Let's do this, Win!
دعونا نفعل هذا، فوز!
We're going live.
نحن سنبث مباشر.
Three, two, one.
ثلاثة، اثنان، واحد.
Hello, everybody.
مرحبا بالجميع.
I'm Master Win.
أنا ماستر وين.
Feel free to send me your questions.
لا تتردد في إرسال أسئلتك إلي.
Hold on, Namo.
انتظر يا نامو.
Is this your solution to my problem?
هل هذا هو الحل لمشكلتي؟
Fortune telling at a funeral?
قراءة الطالع في الجنازة؟
Listen.
يستمع.
At least the food's free.
على الأقل الطعام مجاني.
(With Condolences: MP Eung Wiriya and Family)
(مع التعازي: النائب إيونج ويريا وعائلته)
Win?
يفوز؟
Do you think this place is filled with ghosts?
هل تعتقد أن هذا المكان مليء بالأشباح؟
Just because you don't see them doesn't mean they don't know
مجرد أنك لا تراهم لا يعني أنهم لا يعرفون
you're disrespecting them!
أنت لا تحترمهم!
What? Come on!
ماذا؟ هيا!
I'm leaving.
انا ذاهب.
Are you the fortune teller friend of MP Eung's son?
هل أنت صديق العراف لابن النائب اونغ؟
Yes.
نعم.
Can you please give me a reading?
هل يمكنك من فضلك أن تعطيني قراءة؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
I'd like to know if he's passed peacefully or not,
أريد أن أعرف هل توفي بسلام أم لا
if he still has worries to cling to.
إذا كان لا يزال لديه مخاوف يتشبث بها.
My son, Daeng...
ابني داينج...
He said that if he had to die,
وقال أنه إذا كان عليه أن يموت،
he wanted to die in the line of duty.
أراد أن يموت أثناء أداء واجبه.
And look at what his words got him!
وانظر ماذا حصلت عليه كلماته!
But I've never done a reading for the dead...
ولكنني لم أقرأ عن الموتى أبدًا...
It can get confusing.
يمكن أن يصبح الأمر مربكًا.
Is this true? He actually passed away happily?
هل هذا صحيح؟ هل مات سعيدًا حقًا؟
Thank you so much, Master.
شكرا جزيلا لك يا سيدي.
So, how much do you charge for this?
إذن، كم تتقاضى مقابل هذا؟
You've already paid me.
لقد دفعت لي بالفعل.
Huh? When?
هاه؟ متى؟
With the tasty food offered here.
مع الطعام اللذيذ المقدم هنا.
Goodness me! How are you this adorable?
يا إلهي! كيف أنت بهذه الروعة؟
If I won the lottery, I'd never forget about you.
لو فزت باليانصيب فلن أنساك أبدًا.
So touching...
مؤثر للغاية...
This better be the last time.
من الأفضل أن تكون هذه المرة الأخيرة.
No more fortune-telling like this,
لا مزيد من الكهانة مثل هذا،
especially at funerals!
وخاصة في الجنازات!
Here.
هنا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Why do I smell... summer?
لماذا أشم رائحة... الصيف؟
Where is it coming from?
من أين يأتي؟
Oops!
أُووبس!
My apologies.
اعتذاري.
Can I have some paper napkins, please?
هل يمكنني الحصول على بعض المناديل الورقية من فضلك؟
Let me clean it up for you.
دعني أقوم بتنظيفه لك.
I can't sense what he's thinking.
لا أستطيع أن أشعر بما يفكر فيه.
All I sense is the scent of summer.
كل ما أشعر به هو رائحة الصيف.
And the scent is very familiar.
والرائحة مألوفة جدًا.
Who are you looking for?
من تبحث عنه؟
Don't be upset, Win.
لا تنزعج يا وين.
You still have many more clients waiting.
لا زال لديك العديد من العملاء في انتظارك.
It's not about that.
لا يتعلق الأمر بذلك.
What are you upset about, then?
ما الذي يزعجك إذن؟
I've been having nightmares.
لقد كنت أعاني من الكوابيس.
And nothing but bad luck.
ولا شيء سوى سوء الحظ.
Don't think that way.
لا تفكر بهذه الطريقة.
You have to manifest and affirm that good things are coming.
يجب عليك أن تتجلى وتؤكد أن الأشياء الجيدة قادمة.
I'm exhausted.
أنا مرهق.
Come on.
تعال.
Come on, Win.
هيا يا وين.
My dad said you're a lovely person.
قال والدي أنك شخص جميل.
You help others through fortune telling.
تساعد الآخرين من خلال قراءة الطالع.
The good karma will bring you luck. Trust me.
حسن العاقبة سيجلب لك الحظ. ثق بي.
That's nonsense.
هذا هراء.
I've been doing this for two years now, and I've had nothing but bad luck.
لقد كنت أفعل هذا لمدة عامين الآن، ولم أحقق سوى سوء الحظ.
What are you looking at?
ماذا تنظر اليه؟
You look so stressed.
تبدو متوترًا جدًا.
Give me a sec, Wongsawat. It's serious.
لحظة يا وونغساوات، الأمر جدّي.
What's with him?
ماذا معه؟
Win.
يفوز.
We need to talk.
نحن بحاجة للتحدث.
About what, exactly?
حول ماذا بالضبط؟
Do you know the 'Spooky Hellish Night' show?
هل تعرف عرض 'الليلة الجهنمية المخيفة'؟
The dance show you're hooked on?
عرض الرقص الذي أنت مدمن عليه؟
No, it's not that!
لا، ليس هذا!
Spooky Hellish Night is popular as hell!
ليلة جهنمية مخيفة تحظى بشعبية كبيرة!
Their videos all hit a million views!
جميع مقاطع الفيديو الخاصة بهم حصلت على مليون مشاهدة!
Tong, have you heard of it?
تونغ، هل سمعت عنه؟
It's a show about spooky stories.
إنه عرض حول القصص المخيفة.
So you saw a ghost?
فهل رأيت شبحا؟
Then what happened?
ثم ماذا حدث؟
It's been tormenting you?
هل كان يعذبك؟
That night, I was heading home.
في تلك الليلة كنت متجها إلى المنزل.
I felt like I was being followed.
شعرت وكأنني كنت أتبع.
Gosh...
يا إلهي...
What made you believe that a ghost was following you?
ما الذي جعلك تعتقد أن هناك شبحًا يتبعك؟
I heard a noise.
سمعت صوتا.
- A noise? - Yes.
- صوت؟ - نعم.
Oh!
أوه!
'Spooky Hellish Night, '
"ليلة جهنمية مخيفة"
a ghost story show on YouTube.
عرض قصة الأشباح على اليوتيوب.
It's the talk of the town right now.
إنه حديث المدينة الآن.
Phloengnathitorn is the host.
فلوينجناتيتورن هو المضيف.
He's both handsome and scary.
إنه وسيم ومخيف.
Each night I watch him,
كل ليلة أشاهده،
I can't help but get my heart racing.
لا أستطيع إلا أن أشعر بأن قلبي ينبض بسرعة.
Phloeng... what?
فلوينج... ماذا؟
Gosh...
يا إلهي...
Whatever. So what about it?
مهما يكن. ماذا عنه؟
You guys know I hate ghost stories.
أنتم تعلمون أنني أكره قصص الأشباح.
They sent an invite to be on the show!
لقد أرسلوا دعوة للمشاركة في العرض!
Whoa! Congrats, Namo!
واو! مبروك يا نامو!
Are they paying too?
هل هم يدفعون أيضا؟
Of course!
بالطبع!
Plus, they only want the cream of the crop, you know?
بالإضافة إلى ذلك، فإنهم يريدون فقط أفضل ما في المحصول، هل تعلم؟
No good profile, no spooky story, no chance you'll be invited!
لا يوجد ملف تعريف جيد، ولا قصة مخيفة، ولا فرصة لدعوتك!
Whoa! My good friend's getting famous!
واو! صديقي العزيز أصبح مشهورًا!
What? But the invited guest isn't me!
ماذا؟ لكن الضيف المدعو ليس أنا!
Is it Tong?
هل هو تونغ؟
Seriously?
بجد؟
Did you submit my profile?
هل قمت بإرسال ملف التعريف الخاص بي؟
Whoa!
واو!
Not you!
ليس انت!
Win, they invited you!
فوز، لقد دعوناك!
- Me? - Yeah!
-أنا؟ -نعم!
I submitted your profile to them.
لقد قمت بإرسال ملفك الشخصي إليهم.
I wrote, "The White Knight Seer with his Spooky Tales."
كتبت "الفارس الأبيض الرائي مع حكاياته المخيفة".
They said they want you on the show tomorrow!
قالوا أنهم يريدونك في العرض غدا!
It'll be the first time 'Spooky Hellish Night'
ستكون هذه هي المرة الأولى التي يتم فيها إصدار "ليلة جهنمية مخيفة"
has a fortune teller as a guest!
يوجد عرافة كضيف!
Shit!
اللعنة!
Whoa...
واو...
You must be over the moon right now.
لا بد أنك في قمة السعادة الآن.
No.
لا.
- You're shit, Namo. - What the hell, dude?
- أنت سيء يا نامو. - ماذا حدث يا صديقي؟
- You didn't tell me a damn thing about this! - Listen first!
- لم تخبرني بأي شيء عن هذا! - استمع أولاً!
Tong, help me!
تونغ، ساعدني!
I got you work, damn it...
لقد حصلت على عملك، اللعنة...
- Tong, I told you to help me! - Quiet!
- تونغ، لقد طلبت منك أن تساعدني! - هدوء!
Just hear me out first.
فقط اسمعني أولا.
Stop fighting, guys.
اوقفوا القتال يا شباب.
The pay is very high.
الأجر مرتفع جدًا.
Please go on the show. I sent them your profile, man!
تفضل بالمشاركة. أرسلت لهم ملفك الشخصي يا رجل!
Yeah, you should go.
نعم يجب عليك الذهاب.
Help me convince him to go on the show.
ساعدني في إقناعه بالذهاب إلى العرض.
- It's 10 A.M. tomorrow. - Please go.
- غدًا الساعة العاشرة صباحًا. - من فضلك اذهب.
Just do it.
افعل ذلك.
What was he thinking?
ماذا كان يفكر؟
Dragged me onto that show for what?
لقد جرّوني إلى هذا العرض من أجل ماذا؟
So damn annoying.
مزعج للغاية.
Please don't be mad at him.
من فضلك لا تغضب منه.
He meant well.
لقد كان يقصد الخير.
Seriously?
بجد؟
Meaning well by signing me up for the damn show?
هل تقصد جيدًا تسجيلي في هذا العرض اللعين؟
Are you really going to let this opportunity go?
هل ستترك هذه الفرصة حقا؟
You're good with words, Tong.
أنت جيد في الكلمات، تونغ.
But you know that I'm afraid of ghosts.
لكنك تعلم أنني خائف من الأشباح.
A show like that is definitely full of them.
عرض مثل هذا بالتأكيد مليء بهم.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
But consider this.
ولكن فكر في هذا.
Each of your fortune-telling sessions
كل جلسة من جلسات قراءة الطالع الخاصة بك
takes two to three hours,
يستغرق الأمر من ساعتين إلى ثلاث ساعات،
and you only get paid 169 baht.
وسوف تحصل على 169 بات فقط.
But telling a story on the show for a few minutes
لكن سرد قصة في العرض لبضع دقائق
gets you 30,000 baht!
احصل على 30000 بات!
To make that much from just fortune-telling,
لكي أحقق هذا القدر من خلال مجرد قراءة الطالع،
you'd have to shuffle cards until you cramp up.
سيتعين عليك خلط الأوراق حتى تصاب بالتشنج.
Please think this through.
من فضلك فكر في هذا الأمر جيدًا.
Think carefully.
فكر جيدا.
That's 30,000 baht in your pocket!
وهذا يعني 30 ألف بات في جيبك!
Please go on the show.
من فضلك اذهب إلى العرض.
What the hell are you saying?
ماذا تقول بحق الجحيم؟
You heard me.
لقد سمعتني.
And if it hits a million views,
وإذا وصل إلى مليون مشاهدة،
they'll pay an extra 70,000!
سيدفعون 70 ألف إضافية!
That's 100,000 baht in total!
وهذا يعني 100000 بات في المجموع!
- 100,000 baht? - Yeah.
- 100000 بات؟ - نعم.
So what's it going to be?
إذن ماذا سيكون الأمر؟
Are you accepting the offer?
هل تقبل العرض؟
Fine.
بخير.
- For real? - I'll be on the show.
- حقا؟ - سأكون في العرض.
- Yes! - Tell Namo for me.
- نعم! - أخبر نامو نيابة عني.
Absolutely. I'll do it for you.
بالتأكيد. سأفعل ذلك من أجلك.
You've made the right decision. Let's go!
لقد اتخذت القرار الصحيح. هيا بنا!
Sadhu.
سادهو.
May this be a good night.
أتمنى أن تكون هذه ليلة طيبة.
Oops!
أُووبس!
Alright.
على ما يرام.
For the sake of work, money,
من أجل العمل والمال
and my future.
ومستقبلي.
It's this dream again.
إنه هذا الحلم مرة أخرى.
You want it like this, huh?
تريدها مثل هذا، أليس كذلك؟
You're safe now, Win.
أنت بأمان الآن، وين.
Win.
يفوز.
Win?
يفوز؟
Win!
يفوز!
Wake up! You're running late!
استيقظ! لقد تأخرت!
Phloeng?
كيف حالك؟
Wake up, Win!
استيقظ، فوز!
What?!
ماذا؟!
Tohmorn?
توهمورن؟
Why are you naked?
لماذا انت عاري؟
I told you not to do mischievous things while I'm asleep!
لقد قلت لك لا تفعل أشياء مؤذية أثناء نومي!
Or else I won't cook your favorite dish as an offering.
وإلا فلن أقوم بتحضير طبقك المفضل كقربان.
I'm really sorry.
انا آسف حقا.
I just wanted to wake you up.
لقد أردت فقط أن أوقظك.
You can do that,
يمكنك فعل ذلك
but not naked like this!
ولكن ليس عاريا مثل هذا!
Well, I got bored of showing the other ghosts my goods.
حسنًا، لقد سئمت من إظهار بضاعتي للأشباح الأخرى.
So this time, I want you to see them!
لذلك هذه المرة أريدك أن تراهم!
I'm gonna let this pass for once.
سأترك هذا الأمر يمر هذه المرة.
Next time, I'll use enchanted rice on you.
في المرة القادمة، سأستخدم عليك الأرز المسحور.
Can you enchant us to fall in love, too?
هل يمكنك أن تسحرنا حتى نقع في الحب أيضًا؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
I'm...
أنا أكون...
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
People these days work too hard.
الناس في هذه الأيام يعملون بجد شديد.
Please don't push yourself too much.
من فضلك لا تضغط على نفسك كثيرا.
Take care of yourself, okay?
اعتني بنفسك، حسنًا؟
Now that's easier on the ears.
الآن أصبح الأمر أسهل على الأذنين.
Just leave already.
فقط أرحل الآن.
I need to take a shower.
أحتاج إلى الاستحمام.
No peeking, okay?
لا تتجسس، حسنًا؟
Oh, okay!
أوه، حسنا!
Let's do this.
دعونا نفعل هذا.
Oh!
أوه!
Today is Monday.
اليوم هو الاثنين.
So the auspicious color that makes the seniors adore me is...
لذا فإن اللون الميمون الذي يجعل كبار السن يعشقونني هو...
Whoa...
واو...
It's not a brand-new company,
إنها ليست شركة جديدة تمامًا،
but they've got a good location and orientation.
لكن لديهم موقع جيد واتجاه جيد.
And a lucky entrance attracting wealth.
ومدخل محظوظ يجذب الثروة.
And not to mention...
و ناهيك عن...
The scent here...
الرائحة هنا...
Indian cork trees. A lot of them.
أشجار الفلين الهندي. الكثير منها.
Who's that?
من هو الذي؟
Good morning.
صباح الخير.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
I'm here for a shoot.
أنا هنا من أجل التصوير.
It's just the two of you here?
هل أنتم فقط اثنان هنا؟
Check in with the staff inside for a card, yeah?
قم بإجراء اتصال مع الموظفين بالداخل للحصول على بطاقة، أليس كذلك؟
You scared me, Toh!
لقد اخافتني يا توه!
Wow, Win...
واو ، وين...
Are security guards these days this good-looking?
هل حراس الأمن في هذه الأيام يتمتعون بهذا القدر من الوسامة؟
And?
و؟
I'm afraid I can't go inside with you.
أخشى أنني لا أستطيع الدخول معك.
The energy radiating from there is too hot.
الطاقة المنبعثة من هناك ساخنة جدًا.
I'd be dead again if I were to enter!
سأموت مرة أخرى إذا دخلت!
Well...
حسنًا...
I'll wait for you outside, okay?
سأنتظرك بالخارج، حسنًا؟
- I'll be right around here. - Mm.
- سأكون هنا قريبًا. - مم.
My dear friend!
صديقي العزيز!
I said I'd come pick you up, and you refused.
لقد قلت أنني سآتي لأخذك، لكنك رفضت.
On your bike?
على دراجتك؟
I'd rather walk here barefoot.
أفضّل أن أمشي هنا حافي القدمين.
You're a reckless rider.
أنت راكب متهور.
Come on now.
تعال الآن.
Are you upset?
هل انت منزعج؟
Here. I got you coffee.
هنا. لقد أحضرت لك القهوة.
- Thanks. - Wait...
- شكرا. - انتظر...
Why do your under-eyes look so dark?
لماذا تبدو المنطقة تحت عينيك داكنة جدًا؟
Like you've been cursed or something.
كأنك تعرضت للعنة أو شيء من هذا القبيل.
Watch what you're saying.
انتبه لما تقوله
Did you ask your dentist on your last visit
هل سألت طبيب الأسنان الخاص بك في زيارتك الأخيرة؟
to remove the filth from your mouth?
لإزالة القذارة من فمك؟
I'm foul-mouthed to the core.
أنا فظ في كلامي حتى النخاع.
There's no way to remove it.
لا توجد طريقة لإزالته.
- Good morning. - Good morning!
- صباح الخير. - صباح الخير!
- Are you Master Win and his manager? - Yes.
- هل أنت ماستر وين ومدير أعماله؟ - نعم.
We're the White Knight Seer team.
نحن فريق White Knight Seer.
This sleepy face is Master Win.
هذا الوجه النائم هو ماستر وين.
I'm Namo Wiriya, his manager.
أنا نامو ويريا، مدير أعماله.
Oh, and here's my business card.
أوه، وهنا بطاقة العمل الخاصة بي.
Here.
هنا.
We provide fortune telling and feng shui consultations nationwide.
نحن نقدم خدمات قراءة الطالع والاستشارات في فنغ شوي على مستوى البلاد.
If you're interested, feel free to contact us 24/7.
إذا كنت مهتمًا، فلا تتردد في الاتصال بنا على مدار الساعة طوال أيام الأسبوع.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
I'm Nokphaeng, Phloeng's manager.
أنا نوكفاينج، مدير فلوينج.
Also the producer and creative director of Siam Nithrarom.
وهو أيضًا منتج ومخرج إبداعي لشركة Siam Nithrarom.
Nice to meet you, Nokphaeng.
يسعدني أن ألتقي بك، نوكفينج.
Nice to meet you as well.
يسعدني أن أقابلك أيضًا.
Then, please come this way.
إذن، من فضلك تعال إلى هذا الطريق.
So, what kind of shows do they produce here?
إذن، ما هي نوعية العروض التي ينتجونها هنا؟
The most famous one would be
الأكثر شهرة سيكون
'Spooky Hellish Night.'
"ليلة جهنمية مخيفة."
Any other shows?
أي عروض أخرى؟
There's...
هناك...
'Fiery Tongues, ' 'Gays Go Places, '
"ألسنة نارية"، "المثليون يذهبون إلى أماكنهم"،
and 'Guess Who's Dead!'
وتخمين من مات!
Dude.
يا صديقي.
That's Phloeng.
هذا هو فلوينج.
(Phloengnathitorn: Spooky Hellish Night)
(Phloengnathitorn: ليلة جهنمية مخيفة)
Why is he walking around dressed like that?
لماذا يتجول بهذا الشكل؟
It's hot, I guess.
إنه حار، على ما أعتقد.
But, is his name just 'Phloeng, '
ولكن هل اسمه فقط "فلوينغ"؟
and his surname 'Nathitorn'?
ولقبه "ناثيتورن"؟
Nope, his name is Phloengnathitorn.
لا، اسمه فلوينجناثيورن.
Phloeng is the nickname.
فلوينج هو اللقب.
But his full name is Phloengnathitorn Asvadevadhamasthitya.
لكن اسمه الكامل هو فلوينجناثيتورن أسفاديفادهاماستيتيا.
Huh?
هاه؟
Can you repeat that?
هل يمكنك تكرار ذلك؟
Phloengnathitorn Asvadevadhamasthitya.
Phloengnathitorn Asvadevadamasthitya.
Gosh.
يا إلهي.
Isn't that a bit too lengthy?
أليس هذا طويلاً بعض الشيء؟
Any name is long compared to yours, Win Wongsawat.
أي اسم سيكون طويلاً مقارنة باسمك، وين وونغساوات.
(Phloengnathitorn: Spooky Hellish Night)
(Phloengnathitorn: ليلة جهنمية مخيفة)
Oh, I'll be right back.
أوه، سأعود في الحال.
Hey, where are you going?
مهلا، إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Don't worry. I'll be back in a flash.
لا تقلق، سأعود في لحظة.
Whatever.
أيا كان.
What are you doing, boss?
ماذا تفعل يا رئيس؟
No. I'm not doing anything.
لا، أنا لا أفعل أي شيء.
Don't you have work to do, Job?
أليس لديك عمل يا أيوب؟
Of course, I do.
بالطبع أفعل.
But why don't you approach him if you're interested, boss?
ولكن لماذا لا تقترب منه إذا كنت مهتمًا، يا رئيس؟
You even got Nokphaeng to invite him on the show.
لقد تمكنت حتى من إقناع نوكفينج بدعوته إلى العرض.
Don't let this go to waste.
لا تدع هذا يذهب سدى.
Nokphaeng agrees he's a lovely guy.
نوكفاينج يتفق على أنه رجل جميل.
No comment. I'm going back to work.
لا تعليق. سأعود للعمل.
It smells so lovely.
رائحتها جميلة جداً.
Is this a special pillow to help with sleeping?
هل هذه وسادة خاصة للمساعدة على النوم؟
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Are you Master Win?
هل أنت ماستر وين؟
I am.
أنا أكون.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
آسف لإبقائك في انتظار.
Right.
يمين.
Please wait here for a bit.
من فضلك انتظر هنا قليلا.
Phloeng will be here soon.
سيكون فلوينج هنا قريبا.
So... I don't need to do any makeup?
إذن... لا أحتاج إلى وضع أي مكياج؟
Oh, no.
أوه لا.
Today's session is a podcast.
جلسة اليوم عبارة عن بودكاست.
No fancy stuff needed.
لا حاجة لأشياء فاخرة.
The crew didn't tell you that?
ولم يخبرك الطاقم بذلك؟
No...
لا...
Then, here's everything in brief.
إذن، هنا كل شيء باختصار.
So, Nokphaeng wants the show to feel as natural as possible.
لذلك، تريد نوكفاينج أن يبدو العرض طبيعيًا قدر الإمكان.
And I need to tell ghost stories, correct?
وأنا بحاجة إلى أن أحكي قصص الأشباح، أليس كذلك؟
Would a childhood story work?
هل قصة الطفولة ستنجح؟
Uh, no. You don't need to tell any stories.
أوه، لا. ليس عليك أن تحكي أي قصص.
What? Really?
ماذا؟ حقا؟
We actually invited you here
لقد دعوناك هنا بالفعل
as a guest clairvoyant expert.
كخبير ضيف في مجال العرافة.
Huh?
هاه؟
A clairvoyant expert?
خبير في علم النفس؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Nokphaeng wanted new methods to make the show more interesting.
أراد نوكفاينج أساليب جديدة لجعل العرض أكثر إثارة للاهتمام.
So, he wanted someone with special senses on the show.
لذلك، أراد شخصًا يتمتع بحواس خاصة في العرض.
The storyteller for this EP is Jaab.
راوي القصة في هذه EP هو جاب.
He's going to share his story about being cursed.
سوف يشارك قصته حول لعنته.
And your job
ووظيفتك
is to contact the spirits.
هو الاتصال بالأرواح.
Contact the spirits?
الاتصال بالارواح؟
But the crew invited me here to tell ghost stories, didn't they?
لكن الطاقم دعاني إلى هنا لأحكي قصص الأشباح، أليس كذلك؟
Certainly not.
بالتأكيد لا.
The project coordinator clearly specified that
وقد أوضح منسق المشروع بوضوح أن
Master Win will be contacting the dead on behalf of the storyteller.
سوف يتواصل السيد وين مع الموتى نيابة عن الراوي.
And...
و...
Oh, Phloeng is here.
أوه، فلوينغ هنا.
He'll explain further.
وسوف يشرح أكثر.
Hello, Master.
مرحباً سيدي.
I'm Phloengnathitorn.
أنا فلوينجناثيورن.
Phloengnathitorn?
Phloengnathitorn؟
The one behind the summer scent.
الذي يقف وراء رائحة الصيف.
Has Job already told you that you'll be contacting the spirits?
هل سبق وأن أخبرك أيوب أنك سوف تتواصل مع الأرواح؟
Yes.
نعم.
He just told me that, actually.
لقد أخبرني بذلك بالفعل.
Then, let's get to it.
حسنًا، دعونا نبدأ.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
You're not going to tell me Jaab's story in brief?
لن تخبرني قصة جاب باختصار؟
Oh, I've read it.
أوه لقد قرأته.
But... Job said
ولكن... قال أيوب
you'd tell me his story beforehand.
ستخبرني قصته مسبقًا.
You'll be fine.
سوف تكون بخير.
I'm the host anyway.
أنا المضيف على أية حال.
You just go with the flow.
أنت فقط تذهب مع التدفق.
So, can I have tarot cards?
إذن، هل يمكنني الحصول على بطاقات التارو؟
Tarot cards?
بطاقات التاروت؟
Well, I'm a Tarot card reader.
حسنًا، أنا قارئ بطاقات التارو.
To contact the spirits, I need them.
لكي أتواصل مع الأرواح، فأنا بحاجة إليهم.
Dude, if this EP goes live,
يا رجل، إذا تم إطلاق هذا EP،
my career is gonna be in ruins...
مسيرتي المهنية سوف تكون في حالة خراب...
Come on! You're exaggerating.
هيا! أنت تبالغ.
Everybody loves you, Win.
الجميع يحبك، وين.
So, where were you when I was doing the podcast?
إذن، أين كنت عندما كنت أقوم بالبودكاست؟
I... didn't want to disturb you.
أنا لم أرد أن أزعجك.
How about this? You wait here.
ماذا عن هذا؟ انتظر هنا.
I'll get my motorbike and ride us home.
سأحصل على دراجتي النارية وأقودنا إلى المنزل.
Okay?
تمام؟
Fine.
بخير.
So you end up riding home with me.
لذا انتهى بك الأمر بالركوب معي إلى المنزل.
Be back soon!
سأعود قريبا!
Excuse me?
اعذرني؟
What are you doing here, little guy?
ماذا تفعل هنا يا صغيري؟
Can you take me to Papa Phloeng?
هل يمكنك أن تأخذني إلى بابا فلوينج؟
Phloeng?
كيف حالك؟
Which Phloeng do you mean?
أي فلوينج تقصد؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
I only know Papa's name is Phloeng.
أنا أعرف فقط أن اسم بابا هو فلوينج.
Is it this man?
هل هو هذا الرجل؟
Yes! It's him!
نعم إنه هو!
My Papa Phloeng!
بابا فلوينج!
Hm?
هممم؟
Phloeng...
يعيش...
He's keeping his son a secret?
هل يخفي أمر ابنه سراً؟
Can you take me to him?
هل يمكنك أن تأخذني إليه؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Why can't I do that?
لماذا لا أستطيع فعل ذلك؟
Let me take him to you.
دعني آخذه إليك.
Let's go, Yok.
دعنا نذهب، لا أحد.
Follow me.
اتبعني.
You're still here?
هل مازلت هنا؟
What's this?
ما هذا؟
The Radiance of the Seven Gems?
إشراقة الجواهر السبعة؟
It's the light of a highly virtuous person.
إنه نور الإنسان الفاضل للغاية.
That would explain
هذا من شأنه أن يفسر
why no ghosts could enter the building.
لماذا لا يستطيع الأشباح دخول المبنى؟
Master?
يتقن؟
Are you staring at my chest?
هل تحدق في صدري؟
A highly virtuous soul...
روح فاضلة للغاية...
(Directed by: Siwasit Phondongnok)
(إخراج: سيواسيت فوندونجنوك)
and it says that it happens at 25.
ويقول أن ذلك يحدث في سن 25.
That means I've made it, haven't I?
وهذا يعني أنني نجحت، أليس كذلك؟
You need to seek help from a highly virtuous individual.
يجب عليك طلب المساعدة من شخص فاضل للغاية.
Who is my karmic creditor, that the Venerable Father told me about?
من هو دائني الكرمي الذي أخبرني عنه الأب الجليل؟
Win...
يفوز...
No, you're still alive.
لا، أنت لا تزال على قيد الحياة.